quizfactor.com 2013-11-12

# Privacy Statement - Quiz Factor

## Introduction

This privacy policy relates to the quizfactor.com website located at www.quizfactor.com ("Website"). The Website is managed by QuizFactor Limited ("Quiz Factor").

All personal data collected and customer funds held in connection with the services provided on the Website are transferred to and stored by Quiz Factor on its servers in the UK. Quiz Factor is notified with the Information Commissioner’s Office under number Z3142546 and is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to the Website.

When you use the services available on the Website, you will be asked to provide personal identifiable information by Quiz Factor.

Quiz Factor, as mentioned above, is committed to respecting your privacy and to complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws and has therefore provided this Privacy Policy to help you understand how it collects, uses and safeguards your Personal Information. If you do not understand the Privacy Policy or how Quiz Factor handles or uses the Personal Information which you provide then you are invited to send in your questions using the form on this page and we will do our best to answer your questions in full as quickly as possible.

## Information Collection

We collect Personal Information when you register and use the services available at the Website, make customer inquiries, or respond to communications (such as questionnaires or surveys). The Personal Information we will collect from you may include, for example, your name, email address, home address, telephone number, debit/credit card data and date of birth and other information collected on registration or through surveys which we may undertake.

## How Your Information is Processed

The Personal Information which you provide will be processed for one or more of the following Purposes: (i) to allow Quiz Factor to provide you with the services on the Website; (ii) to process any of your requests for information; (iii) to provide member support services to you; (iv) to market services or products or those of other entities if requested by you; (v) to contact you in relation to the services on the Website; (vi) to notify you about updates to Quiz Factor's software and/or services; (vii) to monitor the services on the Website and your compliance with, and any suspected breach of, any applicable terms and conditions (including, without limitation, checking chat submissions); (viii) if the Website is no longer available, to contact you in relation to the closure of the Website and inform you of any similar services offered by Quiz Factor; and (ix) to support any of the intended purposes specifically stated at the time at which you provided the Personal Information.

## To Whom Your Information May Be Disclosed

Your Personal Information may, for the Purposes, be disclosed by Quiz Factor for processing to any of the following Recipients: (i) to any third parties which provide services to Quiz Factor solely in order to allow or enable them to provide you with the services on the Website, including by way of example affiliate networks, payment processors and data verifiers; (ii) to any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of Quiz Factor's, business processes; (iii) to third parties, clearly identified as the sponsors of quizzes that you complete; and (iv) to Quiz Factor. Any processing performed by any Recipients will, where required by law, be governed by a data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving any and all of your statutory data protection rights and obligating the Recipients to respect the Personal Information and handle it in accordance with the relevant laws.

Your information may be disclosed to government institutions or regulatory authorities if required by law. In addition, Quiz Factor shall be entitled to inform the relevant authorities, other online service providers and banks, credit card companies and other financial institutions of your identity if there is any suspected unlawful, fraudulent or improper activity on your account.

## Mergers and other events requiring Transfer

If the Company should ever file for bankruptcy, or become insolvent, or be acquired by a third party, merge with a third party, sell all or part of its assets, or transfer substantially all or part of its relevant assets to a third party, the Company is entitled to share or transfer the Personal Information and all other information you have provided to the Company to potential and subsequent business and merger partners.

## Direct Marketing

Out of respect for your right to privacy, we are happy to provide you with an easy means to stop receiving email offers. At any time, you may request to be suppressed on our mailing list to stop receiving these offers using the form on this page by selecting the "Unsubscribe" option. If you would like to stop receiving mail or telemarketing offers, please call 0207 932 4188 or write to QuizFactor Limited, 46 Gillingham Street, London, SW1V 1HU

## Managing your personal information

The data you provide to Quiz Factor will be held as you have provided it. You may at any time amend or update your data by visiting Quiz Factor at http://www.quizfactor.com/account, login and click on 'My Account'. There you will find the Personal Information panel where you can amend or update your details.

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us.

We are entitled by law to charge a maximum fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## Your Rights in relation to your Personal Information

You can contact us at any time to obtain a copy of your Personal Information and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Where appropriate, you may have your Personal Information rectified, amended or completed. We may levy a small charge of up to £10 to cover the cost of administration.

## Security

Quiz Factor has implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard all the Personal Information under its control from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All Quiz Factor's employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with the processing of your Personal Information, are obliged to respect your privacy.

## Cookies

Quiz Factor may send you a permanent cookie when you register on the Website. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can help Quiz Factor to recognize you when you next visit the Website and note the other sites you enter via a link from the Website. This allows Quiz Factor to tailor the service provided to your preferences. Quiz Factor may also use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of the Website. You are not obliged to accept a cookie from Quiz Factor or from any other website. You can modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for instructions on how to do so correctly. However, for legitimate security reasons, Quiz Factor may refuse access to specific website content unless you accept the use of a cookie or similar device.

## Protection of Minors

The services provided on the Website are not intended for or directed to persons under 18 years old and any person who provides Personal Information represents that they are at least 18 years old. Quiz Factor reserves the right to access and verify any Personal Information submitted by or collected from you. If Quiz Factor becomes aware that a minor has attempted to or has submitted Personal Information, Quiz Factor may not accept this information and may take steps to remove such information from its records.

## International Transfers

Since Quiz Factor operates globally, it may be necessary to transfer your Personal Information to other companies within Quiz Factor's group or to its service providers ("Service Providers") located in countries outside the European Union. This may happen if Quiz Factor's servers, the Service Providers, or Quiz Factor's group companies are based outside the European Union, if you use Quiz Factor's services and products while visiting countries outside the European Union or if Quiz Factor transfers your Personal Information to its group companies or Service Providers, and you hereby consent to transfer of your Personal Information. The data protection and other laws of these countries may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union - in these instances Quiz Factor will take steps to ensure that a similar level of protection is given to your Personal Information.

## Retention

Your Personal Information will not be stored for any longer period than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

## Information about Quiz Factor

QuizFactor Limited 46 Gillingham Street, London, SW1V 1HU

This Privacy Policy is subject to change, so please check it regularly. Quiz Factor reserves the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation. In the event the Purposes change, you will be notified as soon as possible and where required, your consent will be sought where such notification relates to a new additional purpose for processing.

If you have any enquiry about this Privacy Policy please contact our Customer Services team using the form on this page.

This Privacy Policy was updated on 14/04/2011
